<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Features on Strawberry Pi 🍑</title><link>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/</link><description>Recent content in Features on Strawberry Pi 🍑</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free Playing</title><link>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/free-play/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/free-play/</guid><description>Click the C button in the panel to enter the Free Play Mode. Click the A to record the free-play music in flash memory.
Users can enter the Free Play Mode, click some buttons, and play some music notes. Users may first press the C button on the keypad and wait for the reaction of the LCD display. After about one second, the main page disappeared, and users could press the number from 1 to 7 to emit the sound of music notes from Do to Ti.</description></item><item><title>Predefined Playing</title><link>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/predefined-play/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/predefined-play/</guid><description>Click the B button in the panel to enter the Predefined Music Playing Mode. Click the D button in the panel to enter the Replay Mode.
Users may want to play the predefined music stored on the device. If so, users may first press B to enter Predefined Music Mode. After the display changes, the user can hear the predefined music playing several times. To exit the Predefined Music Mode, the user could press # when the music stops.</description></item><item><title>Game Mode</title><link>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/game-mode/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://ese519-strawberrypi.github.io/features/game-mode/</guid><description>Click the * button in the panel to enter the Game Mode.
Users may want to play the music game on the device. If so, users may first press * to enter the Game Mode. The LCD display will change and show the game page. The user could see the green brick falls down with different x positions. If the user clicks the button before the brick crosses the white line, the brick becomes red, meaning a failure.</description></item></channel></rss>